Chapped lips are most common in the winter months.
But they can occur any time.
Especially, if you're in the habit of licking your lips.
I'm Jackie Silver from Aging Backwards.
With how to cure chapped lips.
Curing chapped lips can be simple and affordable.
And leave you with soft, beautiful lips.
If your lips are chapped, fill a small bowl with warm water.
Dip a clean wash cloth in it.
And hold the wet cloth against your lips, until it cools.
Repeat this procedure about three times.
When the dry skin becomes soft, dip the wash cloth in the warm water, again.
But this time, ring out the cloth.
And rub it back and forth against your lips, to exfoliate them.
Another method is to brush your lips with a soft tooth brush.
Minus the tooth paste, of course.
Be sure not to rub, too hard.
Because the skin on the lips is delicate.
And it can easily bleed. once you've exfoliated your lips. Pat them dry and apply a natural lip balm. Or other moisturizing product.
Specially, formulated for lips.
Remember to cure chapped lips.
Soften the dry skin with warm compresses.
Exfoliate the lips with a cloth or soft tooth brush.
And keep them hydrated with a good lip balm.
I'm Jackie Silver with how to cure chapped lips.